

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- React.js
- React Native
- Vue.js
- Sass
- Bootstrap
- Node.js

PERSONAL SKILLS

Creative spirit
Organized
Time management
Team player
Fast learner
Motivated

CONTACT

P: +358 44 9818473

E: cihanerenler@outlook.com W: <u>www.cihanerenler.com</u>

L: linkedin.com/in/cihanerenler

CIHAN ERENLER

JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER

ABOUT

I am a junior front-end developer who is currently a second-year IT student at HAMK, in Finland. I am proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React. In addition, I have experience working with Vue.js and Node.js. I have studied and graduated as an art teacher from my prior education, where I honed my graphic design skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT TRAINEE F-Secure | May 2021 - Dec 2021

- Improving and debugging design system components
- Developing Vue components
- Improving UX

CHILDREN BOOK ILLUSTRATOR Nuori 2000 Pori | Feb 2018 - Aug 2018

- · Illustrating children books
- Designing posters
- In events working as photographer

EDUCATION

COMPUTER APPLICATIONS

Hame University of Applied Sciences - Finland | 2020 - Current

BACHELOR OF ART TEACHING

Cukurova University - Turkey | 2013 - 2016

PROJECTS

www.cihanerenler.com/#projects